<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MADDVIPR</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on MADDVIPR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Paper Award at TMA2021</title>
      <link>/posts/bestpaper/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/bestpaper/</guid>
      <description>We’re proud to announce that our PhD candidate Raffaele Sommese has won the Best Paper Award at TMA 2021 for his paper entitled “Characterization of Anycast Adoption in the DNS Authoritative Infrastructure”.
The paper, co-authored with colleagues from UC San Diego, SIDN Labs and CAIDA, studies the evolving adoption of anycast by authoritative name servers in the DNS. As a core infrastructure, the continuous availability of the DNS is of critical importance, and the adoption of anycast can help improve the availability of the DNS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orphan Records - Fixing Afilias Zones</title>
      <link>/posts/orphan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/orphan/</guid>
      <description>Our work on orphan records: &amp;ldquo;The forgotten side of DNS: orphan and abandoned records&amp;rdquo; presented at WTMC2020 and at OARC33 raised a lot of interest in the DNS community. Afilias, which owns some of the TLDs affected by the orphan misconfiguration acknowledge the problem and is working on to fixing it .
Afilias to Protect TLDs Against Potential Orphan Glue Exploits</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SuperDNS - Diving into DNS delegation inconsistency</title>
      <link>/posts/parent-child/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/parent-child/</guid>
      <description>Our work on delegation inconsistency: &amp;ldquo;When parents and children disagree: Diving into DNS delegation inconsistency&amp;rdquo; presented at PAM2020 and at RIPE80 raised a lot of interest in the DNS community. There is a new Internet draft on the DNSOP WG that addresses this inconsistency issue: https://tools.ietf.org/html/draft-huque-dnsop-ns-revalidation As requested by one of the draft’s authors, we provide here a similar setup as used in our paper, so developers can test their resolvers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TMA 2019 Paris</title>
      <link>/posts/tmaparis2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/tmaparis2019/</guid>
      <description>This week, Raffaele attended to TMA 2019 Paris PhD School and Conference and presented a poster on DNS Time To Live Mismatch Problem.
It was an amazing experience, with a lot of interesting workshops in the PhD School and interesting papers and posters presented at the conference.
Below you can find the abstract and the poster.
It’s Time To Lie: The DNS TTL Mismatch Problem The Domain Name System is a hierarchical decentralized and distributed database.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poster</title>
      <link>/poster/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/poster/</guid>
      <description>TMA2019 
CSNG 2019 and ICT.OPEN2019 
Related State of the Art</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Conference: ICT OPEN 2019</title>
      <link>/posts/ictopen2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ictopen2019/</guid>
      <description>The MADDVIPR project attended the first conference :) Raffaele presented a poster on the state of the art of DNS vulnerability and misconfiguration to ICT.OPEN 2019
ICT.OPEN is the event for ICT researchers and industry stakeholders. More than 500 scientists and researchers from different ICT Industry come to share information and meet new people. It was an amazing experience and we receive a lot of feedback on our work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World! MADDVIPR</title>
      <link>/posts/helloworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/helloworld/</guid>
      <description>Hello World! MADDVIPR The MADDVIPR website project is becoming functional. In this website, you will find all the information regarding the project, the poster and the paper presented to the various conference and the information regarding the team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About MADDVIPR</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) attacks are one of the most disruptive attacks in today&amp;rsquo;s Internet. These types of attacks are even more effective and more dangerous when they involve and misuse Internet infrastructure and services.
One of the targets of these attacks is the Domain Name System (DNS). The DNS is a fundamental pillar of the Internet&amp;rsquo;s core infrastructure, and its role is crucial not only for the translation of human-readable names into IP addresses but also for supporting plenty of widely used Internet applications, such as e-mail, VoIP, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paper</title>
      <link>/paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/paper/</guid>
      <description>When Parents and Children Disagree: Diving into DNS Delegation Inconsistency Raffaele Sommese, Giovane Moura, Mattijs Jonker, Roland van Rijswijk-Deij, Alberto Dainotti, Kimberly Claffy, Anna Sperotto PAM2020 Passive and Active Measurement Conference The Domain Name System (DNS) is a hierarchical, decentralized, and distributed database. A key mechanism that enables the DNS to be hierarchical and distributed is delegation [7] of responsibility from parent to child zones—typically managed by different entities. RFC1034 [12] states that authoritative nameserver (NS) records at both parent and child should be “consistent and remain so”, but we find inconsistencies for over 13M second-level domains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Ir. Raffaele Sommese (Ph.D. candidate, University of Twente) Raffaele is currently a PhD student in his fourth year at the University of Twente, where his research is centered around DNS resiliency. This involves studying and identifying DDoS attacks targeted towards DNS, analyzing DNS vulnerabilities and misconfigurations, and developing effective strategies to mitigate and prevent such attacks.
Dr. Anna Sperotto (Associate Professor, University of Twente) Anna is assistant professor in the area of Network Security at the Faculty of Electrical Engineering, Mathematics, and Computer Science at the University of Twente.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of The Art</title>
      <link>/state/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/state/</guid>
      <description>Bibliograpy and State of the Art Measurements Brownlee, Nevil, Kimberly C Claffy, and Evi Nemeth. 2001. “DNS Measurements at a Root Server.” In Global Telecommunications Conference, 2001. Globecom’01. Ieee, 3:1672–6. IEEE.
Benson, Karyn, Alberto Dainotti, kc claffy, Alex C. Snoeren, and Michael Kallitsis. 2015. “Leveraging Internet Background Radiation for Opportunistic Network Analysis.” In Proceedings of the 2015 Internet Measurement Conference, 423–36. IMC ’15. New York, NY, USA: ACM. doi:10.1145&amp;frasl;2815675.2815702.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MADDVIPR DeadLine and Deliverables</title>
      <link>/deadline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/deadline/</guid>
      <description>Statement of Work Year 1    Task Description Outcome Lead Date Status     D1.1 Background research on DNS vulnerabilities Report UT Jan 31, 2019 Delivered   Q1.0 Preliminary Quarterly Report Report CAIDA Dec 31, 2018 Delivered DHS   Q1.1 1° Quarterly Report Report UT Mar 31, 2019 Delivered NWO DHS   Q1.2 2° Quarterly Report Report UT Jun 30, 2019 Delivered NWO DHS   Q1.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>